{
    "id": "b095a8c874dd45ecabaeb10d0475f94a",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He always showed ........................... for work late.",
            "description": "To show up is to arrive.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "843f18efc2374ff694b5cbd2a80bc3dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I woke ................................ hearing the crowing of the rooster.",
            "description": "To wake up is to arouse from sleep.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b6738110b566493bbda38dd93f257c42"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich woman is quite fond of showing ............................. her jewels.",
            "description": "To show off is to demonstrate haughtily.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e194ceb498b54281888e73b75ee9b37e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The stalker was ordered to keep .................................... from his victim.",
            "description": "To keep away is to remain at a distance.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "35b7acc1fcaa4233a1576a25be37f13d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was too tired and passed .................................",
            "description": "To pass out is to faint. To pass away is to die.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "away",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ac2ef3fc61c9479090c557e1ba2c5b9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She would finish one project and then just go .............................. to the next.",
            "description": "To go on is to continue.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c3864fcaf6bb45b6bd4057d33ccec905"
        },
        {
            "question": "After dad lost his job, we are struggling to get ..............................",
            "description": "To get by is to survive.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "by",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f85fb956214c434985e6b865228f5ff7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He injured his head and lost consciousness but came ............................. again after a few minutes.",
            "description": "To come to is to regain consciousness.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9cb74f95afd8440681df963a935d8eeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "They swore that they would never come .................................... to that place.",
            "description": "To come back is to return to a place.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8828a60f8bc40c6aa7f9621d51ace29"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susan dropped ............................... yesterday.",
            "description": "To drop by is to visit without appointment.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "by",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce0940a194c4438fa1d93d48df8618d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old car always breaks ............................... just when I need it the most.",
            "description": "To break down is to stop functioning.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c8b1e0bb032f40519e281a3f7f307ed7"
        }
    ]
}